{
    "id": "ee2aebcce13545c6b8d69ed214ed479a",
    "title": "Adjective Or Adverb Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been having a lot of meetings …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1588c25bb9a14e73a6e66e97d8b77684"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is an ……………………… actor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "excellent",
                "excellently"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "feb13666840041fab76e798c168c5fa9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He should be able to do it ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easily"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f3275f86ee534969bef141ee09c28f87"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take it ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easily"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cc88628c143a46cba0bdbbac1f9d816b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is really lazy and ………………… does anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "acc85e869d1a41ea9e1d0fd9a47f9977"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alan was very ………………… of the plan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "critical",
                "critically"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cc8a6d14232346a8affa16a85317d7c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ................................. ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terminal",
                "terminally"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82d34f2acffd4e4e9436ea2452b2f121"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… agree with you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "entire",
                "entirely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc6779ebac3846c98c4cbf1b2bc693ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a ……………………… waste of time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "complete",
                "completely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1aa7c3f8b6f84b82b001bbc1cad92910"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have ……………………… messed things up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "complete",
                "completely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3df9126d40d2474a82b119fee66166b6"
        }
    ]
}